KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



PERSONAL SKILLS

- Emotional Awareness
- Individual Collaboration
- Relationship Development
- Research & Market Expansion

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails (Ruby)
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite & PostgreSQL
- GitHub

LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

INTERESTS

- Weight Training
- American Football
- Specialty Coffee
- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)

CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

- My Portfolio:

https://keiichi031605.github.io/keiichi-portfolio/

Linkedin: keiichi katsunoGitHub: keiichi031605

PROFILE

Ruby on Rails Developer. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about business improvement that has a real influence on people's life.

For the past 6 years, I've experienced Marketing and Relationship Development in Japan, and Production Management in The UK and Colombia. What I really focused on is solving the problems and meeting the needs of clients as well as team members. Therefore, I've developed the ability to collaborate to work in a team and build relationships with diverse people.

I place a high value on **respect to people** and **learning independently** in my life.

EXPERIENCE

OUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST

InverCafé Ltda., Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (Internship)

Quality Control of Harvested Green Coffee Products

- Developed: "Deep Industrial Knowledge" and "Marketing Research"

PRODUCTION MANAGER

The Roasting Shed Co., London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019 (Full-time)

Production Development of High-Quality Coffee Products

- Developed: "Production Analysis & Development and "Marketing Research"

RELATIONSHIP MANAGER

Yuasa Trading Co., Osaka & Fukuoka, Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017 (Full-time)

Business Partnership Development and Account & Order Management Focused on solving the problems for partners, achieved doubling my area sales targets within a 12-month period.

- **Developed:** "Sales & Marketing", "Project Management" and "Negotiation"

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, SPORTS MANAGEMENT

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

Outside of study, engaged in American Football club, learning Organisational Theory & Team Management and Logical & Critical Thinking for organisational success.

PROJECT

"WHATSPOT" (SPOT SHARING SERVICE)

- The mobile apprication that you can share any places or recommendations with your friends so that you get more trustable information for your upcoming weekend!

URL: https://www.whatsthespot.com